{
  "Question-01": {
    "question": "The more you have of me, the less you see. 
    
    What am I?",
    "answer": "Darkness"
  },

  "Question-02": {

    "question": "I'm light as a feather, yet the strongest man can't hold me for much more than a minute. 

    What am I?",
    "answer": "Breath"
  },

  "Question-03": {
    "question": "The more you take, the more you leave behind. 

    What am I?",
    "answer": "Footsteps"
  },

  "Question-04": {
    "question": "What has a heart that doesn't beat?",
    "answer": "An artichoke"
  },

  "Question-05": {
    "question": "I am always hungry, I must always be fed, the finger I touch, will soon turn red. 

    What am I?",
    "answer": "Fire"
  },

  "Question-06": {
    "question": "I am not alive, but I grow; I don't have lungs, but I need air; I don't have a mouth, but water kills me. 

    What am I?",
    "answer": "Fire"
  },

  "Question-07": {
    "question": "The more you have of me, the less you see. 

    What am I?",
    "answer": "Darkness"
  },

  "Question-08": {
    "question": "I am not alive, but I can die. I don't have a mouth, but water kills me. 

    What am I?",
    "answer": "A candle"
  },

  "Question-09": {
    "question": "What is always in front of you but can't be seen?",
    "answer": "The future"
  },

  "Question-10": {
    "question": "I am taken from a mine and shut up in a wooden case, from which I am never released, and yet I am used by almost every person. 

    What am I?",
    "answer": "Pencil lead"
  },

  "Question-11": {
    "question": "The more you search for me, the harder to find me. 

    What am I?",
    "answer": "Silence"
  }
}